Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
- K, general, 1941-1942, Kellogg, Florence Loeb Kellogg, James W. Kendrick, C. C. Kent, R. R. Kentucky, University of Kerwin, Jerome Kirby, E. M. Klein, Robert Kneiseley, J. F. Knight, Frank Knight, Richard Koch, Elizabeth Koch, Harlan Krock, Arthur Krueger, Maynard (Box 38, Folder 5)
- K, general, 1942-1943, Katz, Wilbur G. Keliher, Alice D. Kelly, William J. Kenner, R. W. Ketterer, Mrs. G. Kirby, Lieutenant Colonel E. M. Kirkpatrick, S. P. Knox, Frank Knox, John Kohn, Cyril Koos, Leonard V. Kosterlitz, Ruth (Box 38, Folder 6)
- K, general, 1943-1944, Kanzler, Ernest Karpel, Leon Katona, George Katz, Wilbur Kellems, Vivian Kelly, William J. Kemp, Eva Kiskadden, John Knight, Frank Knowlson, James Knox, Frank Kohn, J. Louis Kraus, E. J. Krauss, William W. Kreines, Milton (Box 38, Folder 7)
- K, general, 1944-1945, Kahn, H. K. Kaiser, H. J. Kandel, I. L. Kanzler, Ernest Katz, W. G. Kauffmann-Grinstead, K. Kefauver, G. N. Kelly, Mayor E. J. Kerner, Robert J. Kimpton, L. A. Kingsbury, F. A. Kirschten, Ernest Klotschke, J. M. Knowlson, J. S. Koelzer, Vernon Kurze, Louis S. (Box 38, Folder 8)
- K, general, 1945-1946, Kabaker, Alvin Katz, Dean W. Kelly, Mayor Edward King, George M. Krulevitch, Walter (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Kahn, Karl M., 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Kahn, Karl M., 1941-1942 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Katz, Wilber G., 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Katz, Wilber G., 1941-1942 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Kauffmann-Grinstead, K., 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Knox, Colonel Frank, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Knox, Colonel Frank, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Knox, Colonel Frank, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Knox, Colonel Frank, 1941-1942 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- L, general, 1937-1938, Lane, N. T. Larsen, Roy Lasker, A. D. Laves, Walter Leiber, Mrs. Fritz Leland, Simeon Lemon, Harvey LeSourd, Howard, N. Lester, Robert M. Levi, Emanuel Lewis, Lloyd (Box 38, Folder 19)
- L, general, 1937-1938, Lichtenstein, Walter Ligane, Marioin Link, George Linn, James W. Lippitt, L. Austin Literary agents Little, David Loeb, Jacob Lohr, Lenox Longwell, Daniel Lorenz, Mrs. F. A. Losher, Sam Luce, Henry Lyon, Leverett Lyon, V. F. (Box 38, Folder 20)
- L, general, 1938-1939, Lavinsky, Evelyn Lasker, Albert Laski, Harold Lee, Curtis Lemon, Harvey Lesch, Lyndon Levey,Lewis F. Levi, Emanuel (Box 38, Folder 21)
- L, general, 1938-1939, Library of International Relations Library, University of Chicago, Lincoln Historical Collection Lichtenstein, Walter Linn, James W. Little, David M. Lloyd, Carl Lohmann, Carl A. Lorenz, A. J. Luckhardt, Arno (Box 38, Folder 22)
- L, general, 1939-1940, Laing, Gordon Landesco, John Larsen, Roy Laves, Walter Lawton, Oklahoma, Constitution Lesch, Lyndon Levin, Nathan (Box 38, Folder 23)
- L, general, 1939-1940, Libby, Frederick J. Library of International Relations Lincicome, Arthur Lindsay, J. Frank Lippman, Leopold Little, David M. Look Lorentz, Pare Luckhardt, Arno Luehrs, C. A. Lundy, Bern Lunt, Paul S. Lyman, George Spencer (Box 38, Folder 24)
- L, general, 1940-1941, Labahn, C. J. Larsen, James A. Larsen, L. A. Lasker, Edward Lasswell, Harold D. Laves, Walter Leland, Simeon Lemmon, Walter Lemon, Harvey Lepawsky, Albert Lesch, Lyndon Lewis, Mary (Box 38, Folder 25)
- L, general, 1940-1941, Lilly, Eli Lincoln University Lindsay, F. H. Linn, Mrs. James W. Lippmann, Walter Liss, Joseph Lloyd, Carl Lloyd, Major Lennox Look Lord, Phillips H. Lord & Thomas Lorentz, Pare Lowrey, Stephen Lutz, Paul Lyon, George Lyon, Leverett (Box 38, Folder 26)
- L, general, 1941-1942, LaFollette, Fola Laing, Gordon Laird, Kenneth John Lam, M. H. Landesco, John Landis, James Langer, William L. Larsen, Roy Lasker, Mary Lasswell, Harold Latta, Dorothy Park Laves, Walter Lazarsfeld, Paul Leach, Paul Leavens, D. H. Leeney, Joseph Leigh, W. Colston Lemmon, Guy Lepawsky, Albert Leppard, H. M. Lesch, Lyndon Lesser, Simon O. (Box 38, Folder 27)
- L, general, 1941-1942, Libraries, Board of Lieber, Maxim Life Lilly, Eli Lindquist, Robert Lindstrom, Frederick Liss, Joseph Little, David Litvinov, Maxim Liu, Delbert Lohmann, Carl Long, Ruth Long Island College of Medicine Louisiana, University of, Press Louisville, University of Luce, Clare Luhmann, I. S. Lybarger, L. Francis, Jr. Lyon, George (Box 38, Folder 28)
- L, general, 1942-1943, Laing, Gordon Lampos, Michael Lasswell, Harold Lattimore, Owen Laves, Walter H. L. Legget, Robert F. Lesser, Simon O. Levi, Edward H. Lewis, Sinclair Luce, Henry R. (Box 38, Folder 29)
- L, general, 1942-1943, Libraries, Board of Lindstrom, Frederick B. Lippmann, Walter Lowenstein, Meno Lucey, J.P. Lybarger, L. Francis (Box 38, Folder 30)
- L, general, 1943-1944, Lange, Oscar Larkin, Beulah Lasker, A. D. Legget, Robert F. Lerner, Max Lesch, Lyndon Levi, Edward Lewis, Russell Lewis, Sinclair Lewis, William B. Leyes, W. A. R (Box 39, Folder 1)
- L, general, 1943-1944, Lindsay, Frank Lippitt, M. L. Livingstone, R. Lloyd, William B. Lockhart, J. B. Logan, Harlan Loew, E. W. Lowen, Walter A. Lyon, Leverett Lyons, Eugene (Box 39, Folder 2)
- L, general, 1944-1945, Lange, Oscar Larmon, Sigurd Lawrence, Muriel Lazar, Lawrence Leigh, Robert Leiples, Bertha Lemon, Harvey Lesser, Simon G. Leverone, Nathaniel Levi, Edward H. Levine, Celia Levine, Leon Levy, A. Lewis, Elizabeth Lewis, John Lewis, Robert Lewis, William (Box 39, Folder 3)
- L, general, 1944-1945, Lippitt, M. L. Lippmann, Walter Liss, Joseph Livengood, W. W. Lochner, Robert Logan, Harlan Loomer, Bernard Loucheim, Kathleen Lowenstein, Meno Lowrey, Janette Lydgate, William A. Lyon, Leverett S. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- L, general, 1945-1946, Lasswell, Harold Lemon, Harvey Levi, Edward Levin, Nathan Liss, Joseph Lyon, Leverett (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Ladies' Home Journal, 1939-1940 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Ladies' Home Journal, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Ladies' Home Journal, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Ladies' Home Journal, 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Laing, Gordon, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Lasker, Albert D., 1939-1940 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Lasker, Albert D., 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Lasker, Albert D., 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Lasswell, Harold, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Lasswell, Harold, 1943-1944 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Lasswell, Harold, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Lazarsfeld, Paul F., 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Leland, Simeon E., 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Leland, Simeon E., 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Leland, Simeon E., 1943-1944 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Levi, Edward H., Walgreen Lecture, 11 February 1943, 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Lewis, Sinclair, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Lewis, Sinclair, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Lewis, William B., 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Lewis, William B., 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Lippman, Walter, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Lippmann, Walter, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Listener's Digest, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Look, Sammis, Edward R., 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Look, "The University of Chicago is Fifty and Famous," 21 October 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Lovenstein, Meno, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Luce, Henry R., 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Luce, Henry R., 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Luce, Henry R., 1943-1944 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Luce, Henry R., 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Luckhardt, Arno, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Lundy, Bern, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Lundy, Bern, 1941-1942 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- M, general, 1937-1938, MacLeish, Archibald MacNair, Harley F. Mailing costs Mandeville, Paul Marshall, John Matthews, Mitford (Box 40, Folder 3)
- M, general, 1937-1938, McCall, Leo McCallister, Ralph McCann, H. K. McClure, W. Frank McCormick, H. Barry McDonald, E. F. McDonough, John McGrane, Vincent McKeon, Richard McKinlay, Robert T. McNeill, William (Box 40, Folder 4)
- M, general, 1937-1938, Meigs, James B. Meigs, Merrill Merkel, John Metcalf, T. N. Meyer, John Miller, Henry Miller, Maximilian Milliken, Carl Millis, H. A. Mirkin, Stanford M. Mitchell, Curtis Mitchell, Karl Mitchell, W. N. (Box 40, Folder 5)
- M, general, 1937-1938, Moore, Carl Morgenstern, George Morris, Don Morris, John Morton, Sterling Mowrer, Paul Scott Mowrey, Don Myler, Edward S. (Box 40, Folder 6)
- M, general, 1938-1939, MacBride, Burt MacGregor, Lawrence MacManus, John & Adams, Inc. Macmillan Company Magowan, Edward Mailings, cost of Marcantonio, Vito Marin, Allan Martin, Richard Masters, Dexter Matsoukas, Nicholas Mather, William (Box 40, Folder 7)
- M, general, 1938-1939, McCarthy, Marvin McCormick, Cyrus McCormick, Robert McDonald, B. F. McDonald, E. F. McEvoy, J. P. McLoughlin, A. R. McMahon, W. E. McNair, Frank McNinch, Frank R. (Box 40, Folder 8)
- M, general, 1938-1939, Meine, Franklin Mencken, H. L. Mentzer, J. P. Metcalf, T. M. Miller, C. Phillip Miller, Douglas Miller, E. C. Miller, John H. Millis, Harry A. Minnesota, University of (Box 40, Folder 9)
- M, general, 1938-1939, Moore, Carl R. Mort, Howard Morton, Sterling Moulton, Harold G. Mowrer, Paul S. Murphy, Walter Myers, Edward T. Folder 11: M, general, 1939-1940 Macbain, Merle MacDonald, J. M. Macfarlane, W. E. MacGregor, Rob Roy Mackie, J. Craig Mandel Brothers Manly, John M. Marquette, Arthur Massachusetts Institute of Technology Masters, Dexter Mather, William Mathews, Mitford Matthews, Rudy Mayer, Howard Mayer, Oscar (Box 40, Folder 10)
- M, general, 1939-1940, McCormick Institute McDonald, Eugene F. McDonald, S. F. McDonough, John J. McEvoy, Dennis McEvan, J. P. McKeon, Richard P. McNair, Frank McNamara, Robert (Box 40, Folder 12)
- M, general, 1939-1940, Meeker, Arthur Metcalf, T. N. Meyer, Eugene Meyer, John Miller, Allen Miller, Clyde Miller, E. C. Minnesota, University of Mitchell, Dean W. M. (Box 40, Folder 13)
- M, general, 1939-1940, Moore, George S. Moore, Howard Morgan, Jay Elmer Morris, Don Morris, G. M. Morris, John Mort, Howard Moss, William W. Moulton, H. G. Mowry, Don E. Mulliken, Robert S. Munger, Royal Munro, David A. Murphy, Walter P. Murray, Howell (Box 40, Folder 14)
- M, general, 1940-1941, Macbain, Merle MacCracken, Henry Noble MacDonald, J. M. MacFarlane, W. E. MacLean, Angus MacLean, H. M. MacLeish, Mrs. Andrew MacMahon, A. M. MacNair, Harley MacNeille, Clarence T. Mahon, Bruce Malloy, Jack Mandel, Edwin F. Marine Midland Trust Company of New York Mars, Ethel V. Marshl, C. S. Martin, Paul Mathews, Mitford Matthews, William J. Maxwell, Philip Mayer, Howard Mayer, Milton, "Midnight Oil," Saturday Evening Post, 1941 McCormick, Mrs. Stanley McDermott, W. F. McDonald, E. F. McDonald, John McKee, R. H. McManus, J. T. McPhersohn, Mrs. Donald (Box 40, Folder 15)
- M, general, 1940-1941, Meigs, Merrill Menacker, Marcella Merriam, Charles E. Merrill, Marie Meyer, Eugene Meyer, John Meynier, Edith Michigan State College Midwest Conference on Industrial Relations Miller, C. Phillip Miller, Clyde Millikan, Robert A. Millis, H. A. Mirt, John A. Mitchell, W. N. (Box 40, Folder 16)
- M, general, 1940-1941, Montgomery, Donald Moore, Carl R. Morrison, C. C. Morrison, H. C. Morse, R. R. Mort, Howard Morton, Sterling Motley, Arthur Mundelein College Murphy, Walter P. Murray, Howell W. Mutual Life Insurance Co. Myer, Clarence J. (Box 40, Folder 17)
- M, general, 1941-1942, MacCracker, Chester MacDouglas, C. D. MacLeish, Archibald MacMahon, David C. MacNair, Harley F. MacNeille, C. T. Margot, Arthur Marin, Allan Marshall, John Mason, Frank Massachusetts Institute of Technology Masters, Dexter Mautner, Sidney May, Stacey Mazur, Paul (Box 40, Folder 18)
- M, general, 1941-1942, McFadden, D. E. McFaul, A. J, McGrew, Edwin McGuire, John W. McNutt, Paul McSherry, Frank (Box 40, Folder 19)
- M, general, 1941-1942, Meigs, Merrill Meinzinger, Fred J. Mellett, Lowell Meloney, Missy Merriam, Charles Merrill, Charles Messner, Julian Meyer, John Meyer, L. G. Michaels, Sandra Middeldorf, Eric Middleton, George Miller, C. Philip Miller, Douglas Miller, E. C. Miller, James Wilkinson Miller, R. Y. Miller, Spencer Millikan, R. A. Millis, Harry A. Milloy, James S. Minneapolis Daily Times Mitchell, W. N. (Box 40, Folder 20)
- M, general, 1941-1942, Moffett, Guy Montavon, William F. Mooney, J. D. Moore, Carl R. Moore, Howard Morgenthau, Henry Morris, Wallace Morris, Philip Morrison, Charles C. Morse, Eleanor Morton, Sterling Mowrer, Paul S. Mulloy, Larry (Box 40, Folder 21)
- M, general, 1942-1943, MacLeish, Archibald MacNair, Harley Maher, Edward Malone, Patrick Maltby, Helen Marin, Allan Masters, Edgar Lee (Box 40, Folder 22)
- M, general, 1942-1943, McCallister, Ralph McCarthy, Catherine McCarthy, Daniel McEvoy, J. P. McGill, Ralph McGraw-Hill McKeon, Mrs. Richard (Box 40, Folder 23)
- M, general, 1942-1943, Meigs, Merrill Meiklejohn, Alexander Merriam, Charles Merrill, Charles Merritt, Carroll Metcalf, B. Meyer, Eugene Michael, Sandra Middle American Information Bureau Miller, C. Phillip Miller, E. C. (Box 40, Folder 24)
- M, general, 1942-1943, Morrison, Charles C. Morrison, Mrs. Charles C. Motion Picture, Facts and Opinions about Mowrer, Paul S. Murphy, Lieutenant (Box 40, Folder 25)
- M, general, 1943-1944, MacNair, Harley Magill, Roswell Mandeville, Maurice Marin, Allan Marshall, John Marvin, Donn Mason, Mary Marasy, Joseph Matthews, T. S. Maverick, Maury (Box 40, Folder 26)
- M, general, 1943-1944, McCallister, Ralph McConnell, R. A., Jr. McCoy, Janet McGill, Donald McHugh, Gladys McKibben, George McNair, Frank McNamara, Robert (Box 40, Folder 27)
- M, general, 1943-1944, Means, Gardiner Meigs, James Meigs, Merrill Meiklejohn, Alexander Meltzer, Edward Merriam, Charles Meyer, Eleanor Mika, Stanley Miller, C. Phillip Minks, Marjorie Mitchell, W. N. (Box 40, Folder 28)
- M, general, 1943-1944, Moore, Edward LeRoy Morgan, Brewster Morgenthau, Hans Mortenson, Ruth Moulds, John Mowrer, Paul S. Murdock, Walter (Box 40, Folder 29)
- M, general, 1944-1945, MacDonald, Janet MacLean, Norman MacLeish, Archibald MacNair, Harley Maloney, Francis Manchester, E. R. Mason, J. Rupert Masserman, Jules Masters, Dexter Matthews, H. B. Maverick, Maury May, Stacy (Box 41, Folder 1)
- M, general, 1944-1945, McCarthy, Sergeant Joseph McClintock, John C. McCloy, John J. McCracken, Herbert McDermoot, M. J. McDill, Mary McDonald, James McGowan, Lord McGraw, James McGuinness McKeon, Richard McNair, Frank (Box 41, Folder 2)
- M, general, 1944-1945, Merriam, Charles E. Merrill, Charles Merz, Chalres Meyer, Eugene Micou, Creswell Middeldorf, Eric Miller, Allen Miller, Lois Mattox Mitchell, Arnold (Box 41, Folder 3)
- M, general, 1944-1945, Moberg, Jerome Montague, Gilbert H. Moore, Arnold Moore, Harry Morgenthau, Hans Morris, Don Morris, Joe Alex Mort, Howard Mortenson, Ruth Mowrer, Paul Scott Muir, Malcolm Muirhead, J. W. (Box 41, Folder 4)
- M, general, 1945-1946, MacNair, Harley MacNamara, Robert Maher, Edward Martinez, Levi Maximiac, Ruth McClelland, David C. McKeon, Richard McMullen, Horace Middeldorf, E. Moffat, A. L. Morgenthau, Hans (Box 41, Folder 5)
- MacCracken, Chester, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Mailing Department, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Mailings, cost of, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Mailings, cost of, 1941-1942 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Maloney, Mary, 1938-1939 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Maloney, Mary, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Maltby, Helen, 1937-1938 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Maltby, Helen, 1938-1939 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Maltby, Helen, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Maltby, Helen, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Maltby, Helen, 1941-1942 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Marin, Allan, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Marin, Allan, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Marshall, John, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Marshall, John, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Maxwell, Don, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Mayer, Milton, "Midnight Oil," Saturday Evening Post, 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- McCallister, Ralph, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1937-1938 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1941-1942 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1942-1943 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- McCormick, Colonel Robert, 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- McDill, Mary, 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- McDill, Mary, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- McEvoy, J. P., 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- McEvoy, J. P., 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- McEvoy, J. P., 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- McKeon, Richard P., 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- McKeon, Richard P., 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- McKeon, Richard P., 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- McKeon, Richard P., 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- McNair, Frank, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- McNair, Frank, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- McNair, Frank, 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- McNair, Frank, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Meetings in New York, reprints, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Mellett, Lowell, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Merriam, Charles, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Merriam, Charles, 1938-1939 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Merriam, Charles, 1939-1940 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Midday luncheon club, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Midday luncheon club, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Midday luncheon club, 1938-1939 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Mirman, Ben, 1938-1939 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Morgan, J. P. and Co., 1939-1940 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1938-1939 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Morgenstern, William V., 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Morris, Donald, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Morris, Donald, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Morris, Donald, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Morris, Donald, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Morris, John, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Mort, Howard, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Mort, Howard, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Mort, Howard, 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Moulds, John, 1937-1938 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Moulds, John, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Moulds, John, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Moulds, John, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Moulds, John, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Moulds, John, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Moulds, John, 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Moulton, Harold G., 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Movies, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Movie material, 1937-1938, Schlesinger, H. I. Proposal for Study of Educational Films by Experiments and Consequences, particularly ERPI Marshall, M. Lee Bean, Donald Miscellaneous, DeVry, H. A., General Education Board memo (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Movies, proposed by students, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Mowrer, Paul Scott, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Municipal Universities in the United States, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Munnecke, Wilbur C., 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Munnecke, Wilbur C., 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Munnecke, Wilbur C., 1945-1946, BOX 44 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- N, general, 1937-1938, Nash, Charles W. National Peace Conference Newton, Nancy New York Life Insurance Company Nitze, William A. North Central Association (Box 43, Folder 1)
- N, general, 1938-1939, National Association of Life Underwriters National Resources Committee Nicholson, Ralph Northwestern Association on Radio in Education Nuveen, John (Box 43, Folder 2)
- N, general, 1939-1940, Natkin, Sidney J. Nevins, Allan New York University Northwestern Foundation, Inc. Northwestern University (Box 43, Folder 3)
- N, general, 1940-1941, National Association of Manufacturers Nelson, Donald New America Newman, H. H. Newton, Nancy New York Academy of Medicine Nitze, William A. (Box 43, Folder 4)
- N, general, 1941-1942, Napier, J. P. National attractions National Institute for Straight Thinking National Resources Planning Board Navy, Department of Navy League of the United States Neilson, Francis Nejelski, Leo Nerlove, Samuel H. New Republic Newton, Charles Newton, Nancy Nichols, Alan Nicholson, W. S. Niebuhr, Reinhold Noble, Edward North Carolina, University of North Central Association North Park College Northern Baptist Convention Norton, S. V. Nye, Gerald R. (Box 43, Folder 5)
- N, general, 1942-1943, National Safety Council Negro Digest Neukom, John Newton, Charles New York Times New York World Telegram (Box 43, Folder 6)
- N, general, 1943-1944, Nathan, Robert New York, State of New York Daily News Nichols, William Nielsen, A. C. Nolte, J. M. Noss, H. F. (Box 43, Folder 7)
- N, general, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- National Defense Proposals, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Nef, John U., 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Nef, John U., 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Nef, John U., 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Nef, John U., 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Nef, John U., 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Nef, John U., 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- New degree, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- New degree, letters about, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- New York alumni, 1937-1938 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- New York Alumni Club Directory, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- New York Times, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Newton, Charles, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Newton, Nancy, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Newton, Nancy, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Nevins, Allan, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Nicholson, Ralph, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Nicholson, Ralph, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Nielsen, A. C., 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Nielsen, A. C., 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Nielsen, A. C., 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Nielsen, A. C., 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Northwestern University's charter and amendments, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Nuveen, John, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Nuveen, John, 1940-1941 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Nuveen, John, 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Nuveen, John, 1942-1943 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Nuveen, John, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Nuveen, John, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- O, general, 1937-1938, O'Donnell, Al F. Ogburn, William F. Overdorf, Eliot (Box 45, Folder 7)
- O, general, 1938-1939, O'Donnell, A. F. Oesterling, H. Carl Omaha, University of Orwick, Ralph Outdoor advertising (Box 45, Folder 8)
- O, general, 1939-1940, O'Donnell, Al F. Olin, Milton Omaha, University, Association of Urban Universities, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- O, general, 1940-1941, Oak Park Public Schools O'Brien, Howard Vincent O'Connor, Basil O'Donnell, Georgene Oriental Institute Otto, Henry (Box 45, Folder 10)
- O, general, 1941-1942, Ogburn, Charlton Oklahoma Publishing Co. Oliver, Edith Olson, Emery Opinion Parade Oriental Institute Orioli, Luis Oskaloosa Daily Herald Owl and Serpent Ozanick, Miriam (Box 45, Folder 11)
- O, general, 1943-1944, Oreamuno, J. Rafael (Box 45, Folder 12)
- O, general, 1944-1945, Oldham, Dr. Oreamuno, Rafael (Box 45, Folder 13)
- O, general, 1945-1946, Ogburn, William F. Opal, Chester (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Oehm, Florence, July – December, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Oehm, Florence, January – June, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Oehm, Florence, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Office of the President memoranda, 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Office of the President memoranda, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Office of the President memoranda, 1940-1941 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Ogburn, William F., 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Ogburn, William F., 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Ogburn, William F., 1940-1941 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Ogburn, William F., 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Obburn, William F., 1942-1943 (Box 45, Folder 25)